{
  "items": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "quizName": "prvi kviz"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "quizName": "drugi kviz"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "quizName": "aaaaaa",
      "questions": []
    }
  ],
  "allQuestions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "questionTxt": "kdsodksokdsokdosakdoskdoako",
      "questionAnswer": "kdsodksokdsokdosakdoskdoako"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "armin",
      "quizAnswer": "dksadkaosdkasokdoas"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "quizQuestion": "gggggggggggggg",
      "quizAnswer": "fdasdasdasdad"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "quizQuestion": "trece novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dksodksaodkasoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "quizQuestion": "trece novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dksodksaodkasoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "quizQuestion": "trece novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dksodksaodkasoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "quizQuestion": "trece novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dksodksaodkasoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "quizQuestion": "armin novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dsdadsada"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "quizQuestion": "armin novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dsdadsada"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "quizQuestion": "armin novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dsdadsada"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "quizQuestion": "armin novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dsdadsada"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "quizQuestion": "armin novo pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "dsdadsada"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "quizQuestion": "fffffffffffffff",
      "quizAnswer": "dsadsadsad"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "quizQuestion": "dsdada",
      "quizAnswer": "dasdad"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "quizQuestion": "dsadadd",
      "quizAnswer": "aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "quizQuestion": "dsdsa",
      "quizAnswer": "dasdsad"
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "ff",
      "quizAnswer": "ff",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "fdf",
      "quizAnswer": "fdfd",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "fdfdf",
      "quizAnswer": "fdfdf",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "quizId": 3,
      "quizQuestion": "fdfd",
      "quizAnswer": "fsdfdsfd",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "novo pitanje u kvizu dva",
      "quizAnswer": "kdaokdoakdoakdo",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "jos jedno pitanje",
      "quizAnswer": "kokokok",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "ggggg",
      "quizAnswer": "g",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "quizId": 2,
      "quizQuestion": "eeeeeeeee",
      "quizAnswer": "e",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "quizId": 1,
      "quizQuestion": "arbddddggggggggggggggggg",
      "quizAnswer": "sassa",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "quizId": 1,
      "quizQuestion": "dddddddddddddddddddd",
      "quizAnswer": "dd",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "quizId": 3,
      "quizQuestion": "aaaaaaaaa",
      "quizAnswer": "aaaa",
      "answerVisible": false
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "quizId": 1,
      "quizQuestion": "jos jedna procjevaavva",
      "quizAnswer": "dsadasd",
      "answerVisible": false
    }
  ]
}